diaperdecisions.com 2014-02-13

# Diaper Decisions

Privacy Policy

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter or respond to a survey.   
When you register on our site, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**What do we use your information for?**

The information we collect from you may be used to personalize your hunt experience and to administer the Great Cloth Diaper Hunt.

**Email contact**

When you register for the Great Cloth Diaper Hunt, the email address you provide may be used to send you Hunt related information and updates. We use an email newsletter service provider for this and you may unsubscribe from future emails by following the unsubscribe instructions found at the bottom of each newsletter.

**Cookies**

Our forum software uses cookies to recognize your computer's browser and save your preferences for future visits.

**Disclosure of Personal Information**

We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties in the ordinary course of our business, nor do we share it with them for their own direct marketing purposes. 

We may disclose your personal information to third parties who complete transactions or perform services on our behalf or for your benefit. Information provided to such parties for payment authorization or verification purposes may be retained by them in a database that is used to provide similar services to others. We may also utilize the services of third parties to verify customer data, such as mailing addresses or to supplement other information we have collected. We may also contract with third parties to host a site, conduct market research, or send you information regarding our products or services, or those of other companies with whom we conduct business. 

We may disclose your personal information to legal or government regulatory authorities in response to their requests for such information or to assist in investigations of theft, fraud, or abuse. We may also disclose your personal information to third parties in connection with claims, disputes, or litigation, or if we determine its disclosure is necessary in an emergency.

**Links to Other Websites**

Our website contains links to websites operated by third parties. These third party websites may collect information about your visit. This privacy policy does not apply to, and we are not responsible for, the practices of such third parties. We encourage you to check the privacy policy of each site you visit.

**Information about Children**

We are committed to protecting the privacy of children and comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). We do not knowingly collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. If you are the parent or guardian of a child under the age of 13 who has provided personally identifiable information, please [contact us.](mailto:info@diaperdecisions.com)

**Your Consent**

By using our website, you consent to our use of the information that is collected or submitted as described in this policy. We may make changes or additions to this privacy policy and will include a history of significant changes as well as the last update date below. If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us via email.

**This policy was last modified on 5/19/2012**
